exootnet.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Exoot

Your privacy matters to Exoot so whether you are new to Exoot or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions contact us. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we're using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users – from figuring out basic stuff like which language you speak, to more complex things like which games you’ll find most useful or the people who matter most to you online. 

**Information you give us.** For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a Exoot Account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address or birthday. 

**Information we get from your use of our services.** We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, like when you visit a website that uses our app services or you view and interact with our games and content. This information includes:

**Log information**

When you use our services or view content provided by Exoot, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include: 

  * details of how you used our service, such as your search queries. 
  * Internet protocol address. 
  * device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL. 

**Device information**

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). 

**Cookies and anonymous identifiers**

We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a Exoot service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device.=

**External Sites**

Exoot is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Facebook Signup**

When you signup for Exoot Account, we may collect your Facebook account information including but not limited to your name, email address, birthday, list of friends and we'll try to predict your location based on your IP address.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect Exoot and our users. We also use this information to offer you tailored content – like giving you more relevant games and contents.

When you contact Exoot, we may keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our services, such as letting you know about upcoming changes or improvements. 

We may combine personal information from one service with information, including personal information, from other Exoot services – for example to make it easier to share things with people you know. 

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy. 

Exoot processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. 

Accessing and updating your personal information 

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. 

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes). 

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems. 

## Transparency and choice

People have different privacy concerns. Our goal is to be clear about what information we collect, so that you can make meaningful choices about how it is used. 

## Information you share

Many of our services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options on sharing and removing your content. 

## Information we share

We do not share personal information with companies, organizations and individuals outside of Exoot unless one of the following circumstances apply: 

  * **With your consent**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Exoot when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

  * **For external processing**

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

  * **For legal reasons**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Exoot if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

    * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. 
    * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations. 
    * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. 
    * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Exoot, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by Exoot Systems Inc. and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy. 

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include Exoot services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.
